இன்று நாம் நமது இரண்டாவது விரிவுரை தொடங்கும்
செயற்கை நுண்ணறிவு. முதல் விரிவுரை
நாங்கள் அதாவது செயற்கை என்ன சில விஷயங்களை அறிமுகப்படுத்தப்பட்டது
உளவுத்துறை வரையறை அனைத்து பற்றி,
உளவுத்துறை மற்றும் நாம் பல உதாரணங்கள் பார்த்து
AI அமைப்புகளின் மற்றும் நாங்கள் வரலாற்றைக்
AI ன். இன்று நாம் இரண்டாவது பகுதியாக சென்று
நாம் பற்றி பேச அங்கு இந்த அறிமுகம்
நுண்ணறிவுக்.
இந்த நிச்சயமாக ஒரு முக்கிய பகுதியாக நாம் பேசுவோம்
ஒரு அறிவார்ந்த பல்வேறு அம்சங்கள் பற்றி
முகவர். இன்று நாம் அறிமுகப்படுத்தும் என்ன ஒரு அறிவார்ந்த
நாம் எவ்வாறு நுண்ணறிவுக் பாருங்கள்.
இப்போது, வழிகாட்டும் நோக்கம் விவரிக்க
இன்று ?? கள் விரிவுரை நாங்கள் வரையறுக்க விரும்புகிறேன்
நாங்கள் அர்த்தம் என்ன என ஒரு நுண்ணறிவுக்
ஒரு முகவராக உளவுத்துறை, ஒரு அறிவார்ந்த வரையறுக்க
agent.
In the last class we talked about rationality.
We will talk about what we mean by a rational
agent. Then we will explain the concept of
rationality as we see or the concept of bounded
rationality which we will deal with. We will
discuss the different characteristics of the
environment in which the agent operates and
we will explain different agent architectures.
On completing this lesson you will be able
to understand what an agent is and how an
agent interacts with the environment. As we
will see in the course of this lecture the
environment is an important component of the
agent design and the agent should be designed
so that it can work properly in its environment.
After you have taken todays lecture you
should be able to do the following:
When you are given a problem situation, you
should be able to identify which are the percepts
to the available to the agent or what the
agent can sense and how the agent should act
to optimize its performance. We should also
look at what are the performance measures
by which we should evaluate an agent to try
to see if the agent design has been successful
and we hope to understand what we mean by
the definition of what a rational agent is.
We will also look at the concept of bounded
rationality which is the rationality that
we will deal with. In summary we will be familiar
with different agent architectures including
stimulus response agents, state based agents,
deliberative or goal directed agents, utility
based agents as well as learning agents.
And we should also we able to identify given
a problem situation the characteristics of
the environment and recommend what the architecture
of the desired agent should be in this environment.
So this is our agent. The
agent operates in an environment. The agent
receives percepts from the environment and
the agent acts and its actions can change
the environment. The agent uses its various
sensory organs so depending upon the sensors
that the agent has for example the agent may
be able to see if the agent has a camera,
the agent may be able to hear if it has a
sonar sensor and so agent can see or hear
or accept different inputs from the environment.
Inside the agent there is an agent program
which decides on the basis of the current
percept or the percept sequence it has received
till date to decide what should be the good
action to take in the current situation. So
the agent has actuators or effectors to take
actions. These actions can potentially change
the environment and the agent can use its
sensors to sense the changed environment.
The agent does the following things:
The agent operates in an environment. The
agent perceives its environment through its
sensors. The agent acts upon the environment
through actuators or effectors and also the
agent has goals.
Goals are the objectives which the agent has
to satisfy and the actions that the agent
will take will depend upon the goal it wants
to achieve.
What is a percept?
The complete set of inputs at a given time
the agent gets is called its percept. The
input can be from the keyboard or through
its various sensors. The sequence of percepts
may be the current percept or may be all the
percepts that the agent has perceived so far
can influence the actions of an agent. The
agent can change the environment through effectors
or actuators. An operation which involves
an actuator is called an action. So, agent
can take action in an environment through
the output device or through the different
actuators that it might be having. These actions
can be grouped into action sequences.
We have already seen that the agent has sensors
and actuators and has goals. And the agent
program implements a mapping from percept
sequences to actions.
We also have to talk about a performance measure
by which we will evaluate an agent, evaluate
how successful the agent design has been.
And finally we will like to talk about autonomous
agents.
In artificial intelligence artificial intelligent
agents autonomy is extremely important.
The agent should be able to decide autonomously
which action it should take in the current
situation. So an autonomous agent decides
autonomously what action to take in its current
situation in order to maximize its progress
towards its goals. So, if the agent has a
goal the agent should try to maximize its
goal too so that its performance measure is
at maximum. The behavior and performance of
intelligent agents we will look at in terms
of the agent function. An agent function as
we have already talked about is a mapping
from perception history to action.
Now what is the mapping that the agent should
implement?
Obviously the mapping the agent should implement
is the one which maximizes its performance
measure. The ideal mapping of an agent specifies
which action an agent should take at any point
of time. We will talk presently about how
the agent should achieve this maximization.
The performance measure is in fact a subjective
measure which characterizes how successful
an agent is. And how the performance measure
is characterized can vary.
The performance measure could be the amount
of how rich the agent will become if the agent
behaves in a particular way or how quickly
the problem can be solved or how precise or
how good the solution is, what is the quality
of the solution that the agent has been able
to achieve, the amount of power the agents
objective may be to minimize the amount of
power consumed or the performance measure
could be a combinations of several of these
factors.
Actually an agent could be anything. We can
look upon a human being as an agent, we can
look upon a calculator as an agent. So, in
order to characterize something as an agent
we have to look at the different characteristics
in terms of the different mappings the agent
performs such as its percepts, its actions,
the environment it operates, the entire characteristics
of the environment and certain other things.
So let us look at some common things that
we are familiar with and look at what are
the characteristics associated with such agents.
We are all familiar agents, so what are our
sensory organs?
We can see with our eyes, we can hear with
our ears, we can smell, we can touch, we can
taste so these are the five primary input
mechanisms we possess.
What are the actuators we possess?
We have our hands with which we can take some
action, we have our fingers, we have our legs
and several other things including the mouth
with which we can take our actions.
Now, if we design a robot what are the percepts,
what are the different sensory organs we can
give to the robot that we can build into a
robot?
We can have a camera with a robot, a camera
with which it can take pictures of what is
in front of the robot and the robot function
or the robot program can analyze that image
and find out salient characteristics of the
environment which will decide the way it should
act. Then the robot can use other types of
sensors like sonar sensors, infra red sensors
etc. And the type of actuators we can have
or we can build into a robot are wheels, speakers,
lights, grippers and any other output device
that we may want to. And then we can look
at a software agent.
The software agent is becoming increasingly
common now-a-days. So many people call them
softbots. These softbots have some functions
as sensors. They compute a function of the
input. So they have some functions as sensors
and some functions as actuators. We will later
look at some specific software agents to look
at the sort of function which they take as
the input and the sort of function they compute
to give the output.
This is a picture of a robot. This is the
Xavier robot developed at CMU it was one of
the earlier robots that was developed at CMU.
Then this is a robot called the Cog robot
which was developed by Rodney Brooks group
at MIT.
We will have an occasion to talk more about
Rodney Brooks activity in the course of
todays lecture. So the basic motivation
behind creating Cog is the hypothesis that
they wanted to build a humanoid robot a robot
having intelligence like a human being. This
picture shows professor Rodney Brooks with
the robot Cog.
And thirdly we have this entertainment robot.
This Aibo robot is sold by Sony. This robot
is claimed to be autonomous, sensitive to
its environment, it can learn, it has different
stages of its life and it can be personalized
according to the environment in which it grows
up in.
Then there are other types of agents like
softbots or software agents. For example,
there are sites like askjeeves dot com which
you can consider as an example of a software
agent. There are various expert systems including
the medical expert systems for example, the
cardiologist which are also software agents.
Other than software agents we have other types
of robots for example, the autonomous spacecrafts
like the Mars Rover and then there are other
types of robots like intelligent buildings
which have intelligence built into them to
decide the lighting condition, air conditioning
etc.
So an intelligent agent must have certain
fundamental faculties. It should be able to
act. An intelligent agent must act. The intelligent
agent must sense its environment. An agent
must sense its environment. If the agent acts
without sensing, it is a blind action and
blind action cannot be intelligent. So there
are certain types of architectures where the
agents can sense and act and the agents do
not do, do not perform any deeper deliberative
action. In fact robotics is about sensing
and acting only. At the outside we only require
the agent to act appropriately. Understanding
is not necessary. Understanding may be important
for choosing proper actions but understanding
by itself may not be necessary.
However, we must realize that sensing really
needs understanding to be useful. So an intelligent
agent who possesses complete intelligence
must be able to do the following:
It must be able to understand or interpret
what it senses, it should be able to reason
and finally the agent should also be able
to learn so that the agent can operate in
an unknown environment. In fact learning is
a prerequisite for the agent to be autonomous.
An autonomous agent which can adjust to a
changing environment must have some learning
component.
Also, intelligent agents must be rational.
In artificial intelligence we will talk about
building rational agents and we will talk
about different aspects the rational agent
has and look at the .
Now, what is a rational agent?
A rational agent is an agent which always
does the right thing.
Now what is the right thing?
So in order to understand that we must understand
what are the functionalities or the goals
of the agent. What are the components of the
agent and we must look at how we should build
these agents.
Perfect rationality assumes that the rational
agent knows everything and will take that
action which maximizes her utility. So, perfect
rationality is prevalent to demanding that
the agent is omniscient or all knowing. If
the agent knows everything and the agent can
reason extremely fast then the agent is a
perfect rational agent. However, a perfect
rationality is something which is not within
the scope of even human beings. We do not
satisfy the definition of perfect rationality.
We are not omniscient; there are many things
which we do not know, there are many things
which we cannot reason in a reasonable time
frame given what we know. The concept of bounded
rationality was introduced by Herbert Simon
of CMU in 1972 in his theory of Economics.
So, bounded rationality says that because
of the limitations of the human mind humans
must use approximate methods to handle many
tasks.
Hence, bounded rationality does not aim at
maximizing the absolute utility of the agent
because that is something which may not be
achievable given a realistic agent given realistic
resource path. So, instead rationality as
we will look at we will concentrate on using
approximate methods where appropriate so that
the agent can take the best action given its
resource limitation and given what it already
knows.
Rational action is the action that maximizes
the expected value of the performance given
the percept sequence to date. When an agent
takes an action the action may not always
have the same outcome. Sometimes the outcome
of the action may be good, sometimes it may
be bad. So, when we talk about rationality
we must look at the expected value of the
performance measure and not always the absolute
value of the performance measure.
Also, we must evaluate an agent not on the
basis of how it should behave in a perfect
case but how it can behave based on what it
can sense. So something that the agent cannot
sense or foresee we cannot hold the agent
responsible for those things. Therefore rational
action in the light of bounded rationality
talks about maximizing the expected value
of the performance measure given the percept
sequence which is available to the agent.
Therefore does rational action means the best
action?
The answer is yes but to the best of the agents
knowledge based on what percepts the agent
already has access to.
Does rational mean optimum?
Yes, but to the best of the abilities of the
agent and subject to the resource constraints.
The agent may have limitations in the way
it can act. The agent may have limitations
in terms of the resources that it has access
to. There could be time limitations, there
could be space limitations. So, given these
constraints given its abilities the agent
should take the best action that is expected
to maximize its utility. That is the rationality
we will talk about.
We must understand that a rational agent need
not be omniscient because it does not know
the actual outcome of its actions. And certain
aspects of the environment may be unknown
to the agent. So rationality takes into account
the limitations of the agent, the percept
sequence that it has access to, the background
knowledge the agent has and the actions that
the agent can take. And we only deal with
the expected outcome of actions.
As we have already talked about, in 1957 Herbert
Simon proposed the notion of bounded rationality.
Formally if we define bounded rationality,
It is that property of an agent that behaves
in a manner that is nearly optimal with respect
to its goal as its resources will allow as
nearly optimal as its resources will allow.
Now we come to another very important component
of an agent. Actually the design of the agent
depends a lot on the environment in which
the agent operates. And the task environment
of the agent can be defined in different ways.
So we will look at several ways of characterizing
the environment. There are two ways of characterizing
an environment. One way of characterizing
the environment is in the absolute sense and
another is from the point of view of the agent.
For example, when we want to talk about whether
an environment is deterministic or stochastic
we must not look at whether the environment
is deterministic from an absolute point of
view but rather whether the agent appears,
whether the environment appears deterministic
to the agent based on what it can perceive.
Environments can be divided into two types
based on the observability of the environment.
An environment may be fully observable or
it may be partially observable. If the environment
is fully observable the entire environment
which is relevant to the action being considered
is observable. All the relevant portions of
the environment are observable.
On the other hand, in the case of partially
observable environments not all the relevant
portions may be observed. The relevant features
of the environment are only partially observable.
For example, consider an agent playing chess
like the deep blue chess playing program.
The agent has complete knowledge of the board.
So everything about the environment is accessible
to the agent. So the chess environment is
a fully observable environment.
Consider again the environment where the agent
is playing pokers where the agent cannot see
the hand of the opponent. So the environment
in this case is only partially observable
to the agent. So, if the environment is fully
observable the agent need not keep track of
how the environment is changing and deliberating
about the environment. So, if the environment
is partially observable the agent in order
to behave successfully in such an environment
has an added task of keeping track of the
environment and reasoning about the properties
of the environment.
Then, if you look at the aspect of determinism
again environments can be divided into two
or three types.
Deterministic environments: In deterministic
environments the next state of the environment
is completely described by the current state
and the agents action. When we looked at
diagram of agent environment we have already
seen that the agents action changes the
environment. Now, in a deterministic environment
given the agents action how the environment
change is deterministic. There is no other
unknown thing which comes into the picture
to decide how the environment changes.
In stochastic environments, on the other hand,
there is some element of uncertainty. Therefore
how the environment changes depends not just
on the action that the agent takes. So, whether
an environment is deterministic or stochastic
depends on how you look at the environment.
If you cannot observe the environment fully
the environment may appear stochastic to you
whereas it is actually deterministic if you
have access to the entire environment.
For example, take the example of pokers again.
If the agent did have access to both the players
hands and all the cards which are there then
the environment actually behaves in a deterministic
way. However when it is partially observable
it appears to be a stochastic environment.
So this is an environment which appears to
be stochastic because of partial observability.
If you look at the game of Ludo it is a stochastic
environment because how the environment evolves
depend on the value which the die has rolled.
So whether the die has rolled 1 or 2 or 6
depending on that the agent can decide its
actions. Therefore this is a truly stochastic
environment.
A strategic environment is an environment
state which is wholly determined by the preceding
state and the actions of multiple agents.
In a strategic environment apart from the
current agent itself there are other agents
around and the actions of all these agents
influence the environment. A strategic environment
is one where the environment is only changed
by the actions of the agent itself and other
agents. For example, a chess playing agent
operates in a strategic environment.
Then if we look at the episodicity of the
environment an environment may be episodic
or sequential. An episodic environment is
one where subsequent episodes do not depend
on what actions occurred in previous episodes.
First of all sometimes certain tasks can be
divided into different phases or different
episodes. In such episodic environments the
one episode may or may not influence the subsequent
episode. So, if one episode does not influence
the subsequent episode such an environment
is called an episodic environment.
Therefore in such an environment an agent
did not plan beyond episodes. In a sequential
environment, on the other hand, the agent
engages in a series of connected episodes.
So subsequent episodes are dependent on what
happened in the previous episodes. Hence,
in this case the agent may need to plan ahead
or base its action upon what happened in the
previous episodes.
Then if you look at another characteristic
of the environment is its dynamism. Environments
may be static or dynamic. A static environment
does not change by itself. So an advantage
is that a static environment does not change
when the agent is deliberating. The agent
does not need to observe the world during
its thinking process. A dynamic environment
changes by itself that is apart from the action
that the agent takes.
Also, another dimension by which we can characterize
environments is by its continuity. An environment
is discrete or continuous. An environment
is discrete if the number of distinct percepts
and actions are limited and the number of
states is limited. If the number of states
is discrete then that environment is a discrete
environment. And the environment is a continuous
environment if the range of percepts is continuous
or the range of actions that it can take is
many or the number of states is either continuous
or too many so that we treat them as continuous.
And finally we can also characterize the environment
according to whether there is one agent whom
we are talking about in the environment or
whether there are other multiple regions in
the environment. That is, if the environment
contains other agents then it is a multi agent
environment. In games when we look at two
person games we usually talk about one opponent
agent. There are environments where there
is a single agent but for many tasks that
the agent does usually we talk about a single
agent environment but there are many situations
which require distributed agents or with social
and economic systems we deal with multiple
agent systems.
Therefore the complexity of the environment
includes knowledge rich environments and input
rich environments. In knowledge rich environments
there is enormous amount of information the
environment contains. Knowledge rich environments
contain lots of information. And input rich
environment is one where there is enormous
amount of input, enormous amount of percept
that the agent can get. And in such environments
which are complex, which are either knowledge
rich or which are percept rich the agent must
have a way of managing this complexity. So,
such considerations in the environment are
complex. The agent must develop it strategies
for sensing or its strategies of attentional
mechanisms. The agent must decide selectively
what to sense, what is more relevant and what
it should give its attention to rather than
deal with the entire complexity of the full
environment. Thus, an agent needs to focus
its effort in such rich environments.
Now we will look at the different types of
agent architectures. Table based agents, stimulus
response agents, goal based agents, and utility
based agents and learning agents. We will
briefly talk about these agent architectures.
A table base agent is a very simple agent.
An agent has to take actions given its sense
given what it senses, given its percepts.
Now, in a table based agent the mapping from
percepts to actions is stored in the form
of a table. Therefore, on the left side we
have the percepts and on the right side we
have actions. And the agent program is extremely
simple. Hence, given the percept the agent
looks at the table and decides what action
to take. Therefore based on this mechanism
we can develop what we call reactive agents
which can take the action depending on the
percept. Unfortunately the best action for
the agent it depends not only on the current
percept but on the percept sequence.
Now the number of possible percept sequence
can be very large. In fact it can be infinite
till the agent acts over many time steps,
many unbounded time steps then it can become
infinite. So this table can become very large
if you have a mapping from percept sequence
to action. In simple tasks where the action
only depends on the current percept it may
be easy to develop a table based agent but
it is infeasible when the correct action or
the best action depends on the past and not
only what the agent sees or perceives at the
current time step.
So, a table is a very simple way to specify
a mapping from percepts to actions but tables
may become very large. And in a table based
agent there is no intelligence in the agent
itself and the entire work is done by the
designer in designing the table. So the designer
makes the table and the agent just looks it
up to decide how to act. So such agents have
no autonomy. All actions, all behaviors are
predetermined and there is really no concept
of learning.
Now, the mapping from percept to action may
be done in different ways. It may be in terms
of a natural table, it may be in terms of
a production system or rules. This mapping
can also be implemented by neural networks
or one can implement the mapping by algorithm.
So, this mapping can be implemented in a rule
based manner using a neural network or using
some algorithms.
So such agents where the action depends only
on the percepts and there is no deliberation
involved are called reactive agents. The term
reactive agent means those agents whose information
come from sensors and they can take actions
through their actuators or effectors. And
we can additionally assume that the actions
change the current state of the world and
the agent can only take some action without
any deliberation. Such agents are also called
stimulus response agents. They have no notion
of history but all their history is encoded
in the current state as the sensors see it
right now.
Now let us talk about professor Rodney Brooks
of MIT and the subsumption architecture he
proposed based on stimulus response agents.
In 1986 professor Rodney Brooks gave this
notion of the subsumption architecture. His
argument was that lower animals behave in
a largely reactive manner. They have a very
little sense of deliberation. Therefore, most
of their actions are reactive actions. And
his argument was that in the time scale of
evolution reactive behavior came much earlier
than deliberative behavior. And he has been
able to show that a number of such components
having simple reactive behavior can achieve
a surprising degree of intelligence.
Thus, Brooks idea has been to follow the
evolutionary path how life has evolved and
build simple agents for complex worlds. It
is a combination of simple agents working
well in the complex world. The features of
the subsumption architecture are that there
is no explicit knowledge representation. Behavior
is not centrally controlled but behavior is
distributed among different components. The
response to stimulus is reflexive and more
importantly the design is bottom up. The complex
behaviors are fashioned from the combinations
of simple behaviors. Simple behaviors are
put together to achieve complex behaviors.
And each individual agent is simple and inexpensive.
Therefore the subsumption architecture is
basically a layered architecture.
According to professor Brooks the time scale
for evolution has been 5bn years. It has take
5bn years to evolve from single cells since
cells evolved to the present day. The first
humans appeared two and a half million years
ago only whereas the first cells appeared
5bn years ago and symbols did not appear until
only 5000 years ago. Therefore his proposition
is that we should look at simpler behavior
as the first step towards building intelligent
agents.
Hence, in subsumption architecture there are
different layers of behavior and higher layers
override lower layers and each activity in
each layer consists of a simple finite step
machine. Now, this is an example of a simple
architecture proposed by Rodney Brooks. In
this system there are several layers. This
is a very simple robot. In the layer zero
there is the avoid obstacles layer. In this
layer there are several sensory organs. The
sonar component generates sonar scan, the
collide component sends halt message to forward
and the feel force component is the signal
sent to runaway or turn around. So layer zero
of the agent is to avoid obstacles. This is
the first layer of the agent which enables
the agent to navigate in an environment without
colliding with other agents. So it is a very
simple behavior of a navigating robot without
using a lot of deliberation.
In the second layer, layer 1 there is the
wander behavior. This wander behavior generates
a random heading. It allows the robot to occasionally
wander. So in the wander layer there are two
components. One generates a random heading
and secondly the avoid component reads repulsive
force and generates new heading and feeds
that to turn and to forward.
Layer 2 that is the third layer has the exploration
behavior. So this has several components.
The whenlook component notices whenever there
is idle time it looks for an interesting place.
The path plan component sends new direction
to avoid. The integrate component monitors
path and sends them to the path plan.
So as we have seen this percept based agents
are efficient because they do not require
internal representation for reasoning or inference.
However, there is no strategic planning or
learning and they are not good for multiple
opposing goals.
In the second type of agent the more knowledge
rich agents we come to state based agents.
In state based agents information comes from
sensors and it changes internally the agents
current view of the world based on the state
of the world and the knowledge the agent has.
It triggers action through the effectors.
And in order to do this the agent does some
deliberation.
So based on the state of the world and knowledge
the agent chooses the action and carries out
the action through the effectors.
Now, in goal based agent the agents action
depends upon its goals and goal formulation
is based on the current situation. Therefore,
based on the goal that the agent has to achieve
and the current state of the agent as it perceives
the agent goes through some deliberations
to decide what the next action should be.
We will look at search and planning. These
are the two fields of AI in which we will
look at different ways of deciding what action
to take in order to achieve the agents
goals. Hence, in goal based agents the sequence
of steps required to solve a problem is not
known a priori. They are not available in
a table and they must be determined by a systematic
exploration of the alternative actions by
deliberations.
Thirdly, we have utility based agents. Utility
based agents are akin to goal based agent
but they are a more general frame work. If
an agent has several goals and it can achieve
only some of them these goals may have preferences
associated with them as to which goals are
more preferable. In this case we can talk
about utility based agents where we have different
preferences for different goals.
A utility function is a very general function
that maps a state or a sequence of states
to a real valued utility. So a state is mapped
to a utility value and we can say that the
goal of the agent is to maximize its utility
or the goal of the agent is to maximize its
expected utility. When we look at the decision
theory we can consider agents which are based
on utility. And finally and very importantly
we have learning agents.
We have said that learning is an extremely
important component of autonomy. An autonomous
agent should have some learning built into
it. Learning allows an agent to operate in
unknown environments. And the learning element
modifies the performance element and learning
is required for true autonomy. We will take
up learning later in this course when we look
at several types of learning that can be carried
on by the agents.
In summary of todays lecture an agent perceives
and acts in an environment, it has an architecture
and an agent is implemented by an agent program.
An ideal agent chooses the action which maximizes
its expected performance. An autonomous agent
uses its own experience rather than built-in
knowledge of the environment by the designer.
An agent program maps from percept to action
and updates its internal state. Reflex agents
respond immediately to percepts. Goal based
agents act in order to achieve their goals.
Utility based agents maximize their own utility
function. And then in order to have goal based
agents the agent must represent its knowledge,
must represent its history, must have some
background knowledge etc. So, representing
knowledge is important for successful agent
design.
Now we will come to a set of questions based
on todays lecture.
Question 1: Define an agent.
Question 2: What is a rational agent?
Question 3: What is bounded rationality?
Question 4: What is an autonomous agent?
Question 5: Describe the salient features
of an agent.
Question 6: Find out about the mars rover.
What are the percepts for this agent?
Characterize the operating environment for
this agent.
What are the actions that this agent can take?
How can one evaluate the performance of this
agent?
What sort of agent architecture do you think
is most suitable for this agent?
Question 7: Answer the same questions above
for an internet shopping agent.